<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120930" date="2012-09-30 14:21:20 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;How serious is your working relationship?&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, September 30, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;i&gt;by &lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/author/maeghan-smulders/"&gt;Maeghan Smulders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; &#x2014; September 21, 2012 &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;In my final year of University, the time came to start looking for a serious relationship: one where I felt loved; one where I would grow; one where I was accepted into a caring family. That&#x2019;s right&#x2014;I was looking for a great job at an amazing company. &#xD;Like my friends, I was focusing all of my energy and effort to find this &#x201C;dream job.&#x201D; But as the interviews went on, I saw many people settling for whatever was handed to them, committing the next 2-5 years of their lives to a job they spent just &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/job-search/i-spy-how-to-scope-out-a-company-before-the-interview/"&gt;a couple of hours researching&lt;/a&gt; and interviewing with.&#xD;I definitely didn&#x2019;t want this path, and I became increasingly determined to find the right company to build a career and relationship with.&#xA0;And that determination inspired a project that changed my life entirely. I call it&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Project_ONE12.html"&gt;ProjectONE12&lt;/a&gt;;&#xA0;a self-created initiative in which I speed-interned with 10 different companies in 112 days across North America in hopes of finding my dream job.&#xD;The experience taught me many things, but looking back, the career lessons I am most grateful for are these.&#xD;&#xA0;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Confidence is Magnetic&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;At the beginning of the process, when I was pitching my project to different companies, I started my conversation with something to he effect of, &#x201C;Hey, it&#x2019;s Maeghan and I would really like to intern with you because&#x2026;&#x201D;&#xD;I was disregarded or hung up on every time. So I decided to take a different approach. With every call, I shared with pride the vision I had, the track record I had created, and the enthusiasm I had for what I was trying to accomplish.&#xA0;To my surprise, these conversations turned. I no longer had to chase companies to hire me&#x2014;instead, the companies were chasing me!&#xD;The lesson here: &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/career/be-fearless-at-work-3-confidence-boosting-tactics/"&gt;Confidence is more memorable&lt;/a&gt; than any resume, qualification, or degree.&#xA0;Have it, and don&#x2019;t be afraid to show it.&#xD;&#xA0;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;You Find Out What You Want (and Don&#x2019;t) by Dating Around&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Most of us put an unrealistic expectation on ourselves to have our whole lives figured out by the time we graduate from college. But really&#x2014;why? Do we expect to marry the first dude we go on a date with? (Or even start a long-term relationship with him?)&#xD;Throughout my experience, I got to &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/job-search/why-a-winding-career-path-is-totally-ok/"&gt;spend time in many different companies&lt;/a&gt; and cultures across industries. And I got to question all kinds of things about my career: Do I want to work in a small, medium, or large company?&#xA0;Is there a difference between working for a male or female CEO? Do I want to work in a non-profit or would I rather go corporate and donate my money to a cause?&#xD;I was able to define aspects of a career that I liked and&#xA0;understand&#xA0;which ones I didn&#x2019;t&#x2014;and this allowed me to focus my energy on where I actually wanted to be.&#xD;&#xA0;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;You Can&#x2019;t Have a One-Sided Relationship&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;So, what was biggest thing that I found out I wanted? A company that would invest in me as much as I would invest in it. I didn&#x2019;t want to waste my time in a relationship that wasn&#x2019;t willing to support my career and goals.&#xD;I found that these one-sided relationships are all too common in the workplace&#x2014;but I also found that it&#x2019;s often because people accept the status quo. I talked with many people and was surprised at how few people fought for the things they deserved, be it compensation, a promotion, &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/career/the-secret-to-getting-more-responsibility/"&gt;more responsibility&lt;/a&gt;, training, whatever.&#xD;What I learned is, in order to make a relationship with your job go both ways, you have to ask for it. Yes, it&#x2019;s intimidating, but the only way you&#x2019;re going to get what you deserve is by standing up for yourself and knowing your value. No one else is going to do that for you.&#xD;&#xA0;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Don&#x2019;t Settle&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Finally, this was the most important lesson of all. By steering clear of the jobs that felt like settling to me, I was able to learn some really special things&#x2014;not just about the kind of company I wanted to be with, but also the kind of professional I aspired to be.&#xD;The journey to find my dream job challenged me to figure out what I wanted, to believe in the company I wanted to work for, to find the feeling of being valued, to &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/career/career-advancement-month-at-the-daily-muse/"&gt;grow in my career&lt;/a&gt;, and to strengthen my commitment to work through the ups and downs of it.&#xD;And so, after 10 jobs, six cities, 47 job offers, and 112 days of working for free, I landed a self-created position with Beyond the Rack&#x2014;&lt;a href="http://business.financialpost.com/2011/06/24/montreals-beyond-the-rack-named-north-americas-fastest-growing-online-retailer/"&gt;named the fastest growing start-up&lt;/a&gt; in North America in 2011&lt;i&gt;&#x2014;&lt;/i&gt;and I know that I couldn&#x2019;t be happier.&#xD;&#xA0;&#xD;When I started the adventure, everyone (including my family) thought I was crazy&#x2014;and I almost believed them. But&#xA0;today, I am ecstatic about my new adventures and truly believe that dream jobs do exist. And no, we just can&#x2019;t expect them to fall in our laps&#x2014;we have to go out and find them.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;It was August 22, 2012 that I got an email from The Daily Muse (my favourite blog) to share ProjectONE12 with their readers.  What made the email more special was the request to write was a result of people contacting them about my story.&#xA0;&#xD;Its been a year since I started and 4 months since I finished. Looking back - I could have never anticipated this.  But looking forward, I&#x2019;m beyond grateful for every single day. &#xD;check out the daily muse/see the original post &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/job-search/10-jobs-in-112-days-my-speed-interning-experience/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;.  &#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="30_How_serious_is_your_working_relationship_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="738px" height="272px"/>
</content>
