<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20111212" date="2011-12-12 17:21:40 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;The count down starts.. &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, December 12, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Oh hey! &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;So this is when things start to get intense.  :) I have completed 7 out of the 10 jobs for ProjectONE12 and I can hardly believe how quickly time has flown by.  I feel so lucky to have been able to learn so many things, and meet some wonderful, inspiring people along the way. &#xD;&#xD;I woke up this morning and was doing some strategy and planning for the next portion of the project as well as, thinking about what I want to do after.....  and I had three thoughts stick out in my mind in regards to what Project ONE12 has taught me... and they are: &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	Curiosity vs. Passion &#xD;	2)	You are as valuable as your network, not your net-worth &#xD;	3)	Staying true to who you are &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;I could go into a lot more detail..... but those thoughts have stuck with me, and been refined as I have grown personally and professional over the last 3 months.  &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;The reason I only planned 7 jobs in advance was because I was anticipating on having the last 3 internships focused on the industry I want to end up in.  And... exciting news, I have figured that out!!! &#xD;&#xD;I am new, and still learning - but I know that technology is where I want to be.&#xA0;&#xA0;I love tech because it's the process of taking something and making it better, and has a broad reach on different industries, and skill sets. I really do believe it is the most effective path to channel creativity and make a considerable impact, and that is what I hope to do in the world as I continue to grow as a business women, and life long learner.  :) &#xD;&#xD;Gosh, it has taken a lot to get to this point - asking a ton of questions, working in 7 different jobs, living outside of my comfort zone, dealing with negative criticism, marketing myself, researching, planning as well as, questioning myself to why I want to be in the industry.  But with that said, I am excited to learn more and stoked that the project has given clarity on where I want to be!  &#xD;&#xD;Regardless of what happens next, I know what type of job I am striving for, and that is what I was hoping to achieve :) &#xD;&#xD;Thanks for reading, watching, commenting and sharing.  This adventure is very special to me, and I am so grateful for every day.   My 112th day is January 20th, 2012 - 3 more jobs between now and then, look forward to keeping you posted!&#xD;&#xD;Lots of love, &#xD;&#x2028;Just Maeghan &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="12_The_count_down_starts.._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
