<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20130421" date="2013-04-21 22:29:15 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;12 things 2012 taught me. &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, January 25, 2013&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 A TIGER DOESN&#x2019;T LOSE SLEEP OVER THE OPINION OF A SHEEP&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Somethings are not important. Realistically, life is a mess and nothing is fair. I have no control over the thoughts, opinions and actions of others. Yet, I still worried about upsetting or letting people down. &#xD;&#xD;I think women struggle with this more than men.. but my mentor always told me.. &#x201C;Maeghan, it doesn&#x2019;t matter [what other people think]. The less you give a damn.. the happier you will be.&#x201D; It wasn&#x2019;t until this year that I fully understood worrying will never change the outcome, so don&#x2019;t lose sleep over it. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: It&#x2019;s important to listen and respect different perspectives, but you shouldn&#x2019;t compare or be controlled by the opinion of others.  Be confident in yourself and what you can do. &#x2028;&#x2028;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;11) ENVIRONMENTAL INFLUENCE &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I learned that the right environment accelerates the time and ability to produce good work; the right people in that environment enrich the thoughts I had; and, having the right reason to work produced the greatest results.  &#xD;&#xD;My surroundings are something I can control and have more influence over me than I realized. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: Find an environment where you can solve problems creatively and execute them. You don&#x2019;t have to stay in a place you are not growing. &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 NEVER WANT TO BE AVERAGE&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I have nothing against being average but believe no one should aspire or settle to be. &#xD;&#xD;Why? Because you&#x2019;ll never be questioned about it!  All of a sudden, 20 years from now, you&#x2019;ll find yourself in good company with everyone who lives an unremarkably average life.&#xD; &#xD;In 20 years, this is going to be a problem. I was watching a &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WMF-Z74C1QE"&gt;TEDTalk&lt;/a&gt; about how droids are going to take our jobs in the future.... 1) omg! 2) average is a dying breed.&#xD;&#xD;As James Altucher says, &lt;a href="http://techcrunch.com/2013/01/12/10-reasons-why-2013-will-be-the-year-you-quit-your-job/"&gt;Average is replaceable&lt;/a&gt;.. Jobs that existed 20 years ago don&#x2019;t exist today because of the technology advancements we&#x2019;ve made.  Our future in the workforce will be measured by the impact we have to change the lives of those around us. Moreover, to make our world a better place. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson:&lt;/b&gt; Be you, strive to be better and put yourself out there every chance you can. Commit yourself to constant improvement. Never settle being just ok. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 DON&#x2019;T WAIT TO FIGURE OUT WHO YOU ARE&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;How long are you willing to wait before you are smart enough, strong enough, brave enough and quick enough to achieve the things you want to?&#x2028;&#x2028;Quitting my college job was one of the scariest things because I had no idea what I wanted to do post graduation... I didn&#x2019;t know what I was good at, what was out there or what I would enjoy.  However, taking action to experience a variety of different jobs and putting myself out there not only built my confidence, it gave me clarity to be the kind of person I wanted to be.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson: &lt;/b&gt;Don&#x2019;t wait to figure yourself out. Get out there and let the experience give direction to the person you want to be. &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 GIVE UP ON BLAME &amp; EXCUSES&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I find we have an unbelievable tolerance for blame and excuses.  &#xD;&#xD;This year, I started cutting people off that were doing it and asked them to take responsibility for solving the problem.  It was interesting to see the response... often they tried to continue passing the blame but the more it happened, the more I realized the time that was being wasted.  &#xD;&#xD;If there are constructive reasons to why something wasn&#x2019;t done or blame passed to others..  don&#x2019;t waste time complaining... use those points find to a solution. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: Before complaining or making excuses - think about making a plan to how you are going to fix the problem. I hope that if I am caught - someone calls me out on it.  We are all in this together. &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 MAKE DO WITH LESS&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Whenever I am stuck on a project, or trying to tackle something that isn&#x2019;t getting the support it needs - I try to act, think and execute like an underdog*. Why? Because if you are building from the ground up with the tools available, you don&#x2019;t realize what you can and can&#x2019;t do. The focus shifts from the walls around the problem to new creative solutions.  Effectively.. you just do it!&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson: &lt;/b&gt;Don&#x2019;t wait for the tools that make the task easy, get started and make the best with the tools you have.  Build people, value and belief behind the cause. The rest of what you need will come... It always does. &#x2028;*lesson learned from friends at facebook. &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 SPEAK NOW &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;What will you do with your voice? &#xD;&#xD;Ask for help? Negotiate a raise? Teach others something they don&#x2019;t know? Ask for something you want?  Tell someone how much you care?  &#xD;&#xD;Most people don&#x2019;t get to experience new opportunity because they are too afraid to speak up.  &#xD;&#xD;Dan Martell wrote a &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://blog.clarity.fm/the-best-things-come-to-those-who-ask-entrepreneur-advice/"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; recently that sums it up well - You can&#x2019;t be afraid of looking stupid, damaging your pride, getting in trouble or asking for what you want.  There are advantages of being bold: leadership; opportunity; recognition; and, faith from others.  These are not favours that get handed out as gifts at your birthday party... they are things you grasp.  &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;2013 Lesson: &lt;/b&gt;No one else will ask/speak for you. And really... what is the worst that can happen? &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 VALUE YOU &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;This is probably the most important lesson our education system is overlooking.. being able to understand and evaluate one's worth. &#xD;&#xD;Everything has a price tag these days, including our time and experience.  As I exited university and started pitching my plan to &#x201C;work for free&#x201D; as part of my job search... every CEO asked me.. &#x201C;What value can you bring to us&#x201D;.  At first... i had no idea... I just knew I would be grateful for the chance to try.  But what sold the pitch was understanding what value I brought to the table. &#xD;&#xD;Experience, background, strengths, weaknesses, interests etc.  What would people pay to have someone like you work? Ask around. Get different opinions, and be confident in what you have to offer.  This is the only way you will know if you are growing, being valued and where you need to focus on improvement.   &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson: &lt;/b&gt;Knowing your worth shows confidence in your abilities, not your resume. &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 STAY CONNECTED&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;A wise friend once told me &#x201C;its not about your net-worth, its about your network&#x201D; and everyday that proves to be more true.&#xD;&#xD;In university, I met a TON of people at different events on and off campus.. but moving across the country made me feel like as though I was starting from scratch. &#xD;&#xD;Proximity does have impact however, keeping in touch is as important.  Last year, I made a list: people I look up to; people who have supported me; contacts I hope to work with in the future; and, friends/family who I care about.  &#xD;&#x2028;I started sending updates....not necessarily facebook status updates.. but tailored messages to what was going on in the life of Maeghan.  The people who supported me responded quickly and wholeheartedly with any challenges I faced - no matter the distance.  The people who I admired acknowledged the milestones achieved over the year and suggested ways to be better. The contacts I hoped to work with in the future asked me questions as well as offered their help. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: Find ways to build and maintain relationships. People are valuable no matter where you are.  &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 PICKUP BALL - DIVERSIFY YOUR TEAM&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I used to play competitive basketball and my coach always said be strategic in picking your team... be careful not to draft too many players with the same skills, look for a balance in experience, ego and background - this is how you build a team that wins championships. &#xD;&#xD;The same concept applies to your personal &#x201C;dream team&#x201D;... ie: mentors and friends. The questions, the conversations and support you have are influenced by the people you surround yourself with.    &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson: &lt;/b&gt;Be strategic and and diverse with who you want in your life. Work together as a team to achieve great things. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 BE CURIOUS &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#x201C;I&#x2019;m bored&#x201D; is a pointless thing to say. We live in a world gifting a vast opportunity that I can assume we&#x2019;ve only seen/experienced less than 1% of.  When I&#x2019;m asked about &#x201C;dream jobs&#x201D;, extra-curricular projects or building houses in Mexico... i say I do them because I have the curiosity to find them... and just do it. &#xD;&#xD;Don&#x2019;t be so critical in life and allow space to imagine, dream and try new things.  Don&#x2019;t just do it once... push yourself to be curious all the time.  Finding your passion is so 1999, curiosity is what fuels the drive to do bigger and better things.  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: Live outside of your job. Live great stories so you can share with others.  &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	HAPPINESS IS PURSUED &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;If asked &#x201C;what makes you happy..&#x201D; would you hesitate to think? Or do you know?&#xD;&#xD;People often comment on how I am never not smiling.. or ask if I ever get angry.. (which I do!) but my answer is simply: I wake up every morning and know I am going to do one of the things that makes me happy.&#xD;&#xD;Working on projects I love; spending time with people I care about; experiencing places or things I&#x2019;ve never before; eating ice cream; and, telling stories are highlights in my life. &#xD;&#xD;To me, this is the meaning of life. When I can think confidently and quickly about things I love and be creative in ways that gets me excited.. I know, with a smile I am pursuing happiness. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;2013 Lesson:&lt;/b&gt; Find what makes you happy, write it down and make time for it to happen. Happiness doesn&#x2019;t find you, you find it.  &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;2013... I am ready to kick ass.  :) Let&#x2019;s do this. &#xD;&#x2028;Just Maeghan &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="25_12_things_2012_taught_me._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
