<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120401" date="2012-04-01 08:54:22 -0600"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Ending a chapter and starting a new one.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, September 10, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Yesterday was the 2nd hardest day of my life to date.  &#xD;&#xD;It was my last day at Calvert Home Mortgage,  a company I have been employed at for the last 10 years of my life.  Now when I say &#x201C;It was like family there&#x201D;, it really was.  My bosses and coworkers have seen me through all the major milestones in my life thus far: graduating from homeschooling, learning how to wear make-up, getting my drivers license, sending me to professional development courses, moving to college, helping me with homework, supporting my extra curricular efforts, and finally watching me walk the stage at my first EVER graduation.... at Mount Royal University. &#xD;&#xD;Gosh... it is crazy to look back over the years and see how much I have grown up in the company. I started working when there was 3 people in the office, since then they have employed 16. It used to operate out of a house in Willow Park.....I would work in my PJ pants, a hoodie and support a TERRIBLE hair cut (it was a man hair doo... don&#x2019;t know what I was thinking). Now, you can find the company in a condo bay close to downtown and have to dress business like to work there!&#xD;&#xD;The hardest thing for me to see is all the schedules, organizational changes, marketing materials and procedures that I helped implement years ago are still used in daily operations today.  I have taught people there, and learned so much more from the maturity and responsibility that I was so generously given to me by my coworkers and bosses since a young age.  And yesterday, I said goodbye to it all. &#xD;&#xD;I was thinking of writing this entry yesterday, but I had a bit of a emotional breakdown...and couldn&#x2019;t write.  It was so terrible to hand off everything that I had been working on, cleaning out my desk and walking out the door for the last time.  I honestly felt my heart breaking. &#xD;&#xD;I was venting to a mentor of mine how scared I am to leave, and his response was simply - its ok to be scared. Like jumping out of airplanes or asking boys out, it's not worth doing unless you're a little bit afraid of the consequences of failing.  &#xD;&#xD;That made me laugh a bit... not just about the asking boys out bit, but the thought that I knew I would be scared when I started planning the project, yet I continued planning. I always told myself to mentally prepare for the possibility that  &#x201C;this could very well blow up in my face...&#x201D; but my conscience has always been more optimistic. &#xD;&#xD;Yesterday, after reliving the scene from Disney&#x2019;s Tangled where Rapunzel is SO happy to have left the tower, then so depressed that she did  (You can see the video.. you will laugh.. I actually do this - &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UTHmHZaheC4"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UTHmHZaheC4&lt;/a&gt;) I came to the conclusion that everything is going to be alright, this project may be an &#x201C;epic fail&#x201D; but I will never know until I try, and to bring in the optimistic conscience... I know the experience I gain from losing something, will be more rewarding than winning because I will have a better understanding on how I can continue to push myself to be better.  &#xD;&#xD;I somehow found comfort from the most random places that reinforced what I was doing was the right thing for me.  My sister posted on her facebook status:&#xD;&#xD;&#x201C;Improvement- An act of making or becoming better; a process, change, or addition, by which the value or excellence of a thing is increased; that is which such addition consists or by which anything is made better.&#x201D;&#xD;&#xD;My Auntie sent me a text message asking how I was doing after my last day... and I told her the truth.  In her response she told me:&#xD;&#xD;&#x201C;Maeghan, look ahead with excitement and behind with gratitude.  I am sure there is no one at your age that can say they have worked 10 years for one company.  AMAZING! Not many will be able to say that in their lifetime.  Hold your head high and embrace what lies ahead!&#x201D; &#xD;&#xD;I was just finishing reading the book Good to Great by Jim Collins and on page 208 he talks about a girl who did very well in her studies but didn&#x2019;t want to take just any job, she wanted to find a job that held meaning and purpose so she could strive to be great.   Because when you believe in the purpose of your work deeply enough, it is impossible to not try to make it great.  &#xD;&#xD;These thoughts give me courage, and strength to work hard and keep pushing forward.  My goal is to find a career that I am passionate about and no matter the outcome, I am ending a chapter in my life today that I will forever be grateful for and am starting tomorrow with enthusiasm, excitement and desire to grow.   &#xD;&#xD;:) Thanks for reading. I know it took me a long time to figure this out with the support and encouragement of others, but know that If YOU ever want to do something to find your true passion - I am your #1 fan to cheer you on. I know its hard, but change is never easy. &#xD;&#xD;Much &lt;3&#xD;&#x2028;Just Maeghan &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD; &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="10_Ending_a_chapter_and_starting_a_new_one._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
