<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120401" date="2012-04-01 10:28:06 -0600"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Beyond an adventure.. maybe a rack.   &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, April 1, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Holy time goes by quickly. Over the week I found myself sharing stories of ProjectONE12   and can&#x2019;t believe all the adventures that have developed since I decided to do this.  Some are good, some are bad and of course... some are ugly, but looking back brings a smile and fond memories of my life from a suit case. &#xD;&#xD;Its weird... this project has really influenced maturity and defined me. Now that I am reaching the home stretch.. Job #10, I can feel and see how my thoughts and confidence have changed.  I guess that is a good thing... I think this is what it feels like to grow up. &#xD;&#xD;Job #10 brings me to Montreal working at &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://business.financialpost.com/2011/06/24/montreals-beyond-the-rack-named-north-americas-fastest-growing-online-retailer/"&gt;Beyond the Rack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; - a company I have loved and shopped with for the last 2 years.   I can&#x2019;t even begin to explain how different this internship has been from the rest.  First off, when I was pitching the idea to the CEO about being apart of the ProjectONE12... he didn&#x2019;t believe the value of just one week. But something I said stood out and he connected me to the VP of the department I wanted to work for.  After pitching a 2nd time and having a couple of conference calls... I got the job and approval to come work for a month and help out with their annual warehouse sale. &#xD;&#xD;Now my excitement level after that phone call... on a scale of 1-10 was probably sitting at around 11.5.... I was ecstatic that they were giving me the chance and believed in what I had to say (because I really do understand that it is a lot of work to have someone come in for such a short period of time).  So on March 17th, I flew east to Montreal for the first time to complete a temporary internship for the last time :) &#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;ve been here two weeks and adventure always seems to find a way into my schedule lol. I can share this story since I told my mom already.. but when I got here, the place I was staying turned out to be an unsafe atmosphere.  12 hours after landing,  I was homeless, in a city that I had never been before and stressed that I had to meet my new boss in the state of exhaustion, anxiety and fear.  &#xD;&#xD;But this is where attitude saves all - I talked to my best friend who calmed me down. I told myself that what ever happened.. the only thing I was in control of was my attitude and how I reacted to my surroundings.  And you know what... everything worked out in the end. I got a place to stay as well as delivered a solid first impression to my boss which is all I could have asked for. &#xD;&#xD;That Monday brought a new challenge for me as I was responsible for managing 6 new employees on my first day.  This is my first internship where I am responsible for others, but also my first internship working with employees who speak a different language.  :S I aspire to speak french one day... but for now.. sign language and hand drawn diagrams are my tools to communicate. &#xD;&#xD;What makes this experience really exciting for me is that my bosses are fantastic. They are all extremely smart and have unique previous experience to joining the team.  Beyond the Rack went from 2 employees to 300+ in less than 5 years with over a million customers in that timeframe.  I am getting exposure to learn from some bright lights in the space and show them what I can do.&#xD;&#xD;But It is also a lot of pressure... and you know me.. I put quite a bit more on myself.  But the last 9 companies I worked for have shared new skills, confidence and desire to dream big... so as problems arise, I know I can find a way to solve them. &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;My next two weeks here are looking pretty busy, the annual sale is April 12 - 15th and attracts a couple thousand people during that weekend.  I&#x2019;m learning a lot, growing everyday and can&#x2019;t wait to share with you my last day.  Big things planned next... life is truly what you make it... so make it right for you. &#xD;&#xD;Thanks for the support, love, care, text messages &amp; emails.  I am so lucky and I can&#x2019;t thank you enough for believing in what I am trying to do. :)&#x2028;&#x2028;Much &lt;3&#xD;&#xD;Just Maeghan. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&#x201C;Seize this very minute; What you can do, or dream you can, begin it; Boldness has a genius, power and magic in it.&#x201D;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Johann Wolfgang von Goethe  &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="1_Beyond_an_adventure.._maybe_a_rack._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="702px" height="412px"/>
</content>
