<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20130423" date="2013-04-24 02:12:05 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;What I learned from my last #$*@ up. &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, 23 April, 2013&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;&#xD;I&#x2019;m young, I&#x2019;m stupid and I make mistakes. &#xD;&#xD;After walking something like 30 blocks.. talking to myself and waving my hands excessively in the air (&lt;/b&gt;kind of like Tom Cruise in Jerry McGuire&lt;b&gt;)..... I find myself sitting at &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://notman.org/en/"&gt;Notman House&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; talking to my friend &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/zdesroches"&gt;Zoe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; - she is always so supportive.  The conclusion of our talk was unintended, but this is what I learned from my last #$(@ up... &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;I&#x2019;ll Never Do That Again! &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;I can&#x2019;t even begin to describe how terrible I felt for 8 hours straight... seriously.. 8 hours.. &#xD;Although my nerves stuck around longer then welcome... the lesson I learned was almost instant.  I can&#x2019;t change what I&#x2019;ve done, I can only do the best with what I have... and be honest moving forward.   &#xD;&#xD;Crash fast, build faster and let your grief go. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;I&#x2019;m Glad I Put Myself Out There And Took A Risk. God Hates A Coward. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;I tried something... and it didn&#x2019;t work...... shit. &#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;m not going say it&#x2019;s easy to be the person standing on the edge preaching that you have the answer... especially when no one asked you a question... &#xD;&#xD;But I am glad I made myself vulnerable and known as someone who cares.  I&#x2019;ll continue to search for answers and share my ideas... no matter how stupid or naive they are. I am the girl who stood up and spoke... not the one who sat back and watched. &#xD;&#xD;Cowards don&#x2019;t steer change... it&#x2019;s the people who are brave enough that do.  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;I Think I Am Smarter Then That Now &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;It&#x2019;s hard to tell sometimes... but experience is a great thing. &#xD;&#xD;Being able to draw from past events and apply them to other situations makes me feel like I&#x2019;m wiser than before.   I&#x2019;m able to predict potential outcomes from what I&#x2019;ve learned but also view obstacles from a different point of view. &#xD;&#xD;Some of the most interesting people I know say they went through years of #$%@ up&#x2019;s to get to where they are today..  &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;So I guess in short, I&#x2019;m a beginner.  I&#x2019;m young, stupid and make mistakes..... but it&#x2019;s ok - even the great start there too. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;___&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;I don&#x2019;t think my blog is life changing or NY Times worthy.. but it&#x2019;s honest and from the heart.&#xD;&#xD;thanks for reading.   &#xD;&#xD;Just Maeghan &#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="23_What_I_learned_from_my_last_$_%40_up._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
