<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20111101" date="2011-11-01 22:25:20 -0600"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Working in the (m)AD industry!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, October 22, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;My time in Toronto went by so quick! I can&#x2019;t even believe it. &#xD;&#xD;I was very lucky to spend 2 weeks working for BBDO, an international advertising agency in their Canadian division based in the heart of Toronto. &#xD;&#xD;It was really cool, I got to see how television, print, radio, online advertisements are created for some of the biggest campaigns in Canada.  BBDO represents brands like: Doritos, Lays Chips, Pepsi, Mercedes Benz, Mountain Dew, Royal Bank of Canada, Starbursts, Tostitos, Spitz, Tropicana, Gatorade, Quaker, Smart Car and Starbucks to name a few.  &#xD;&#xD;I got to work my first day and the BBDO office is in Downtown Toronto on Bloor Street &#x2013; which is the trendy awesome high class business district.. and I got there 20 min early.  So I thought I would sit and wait on the main floor till like five to 9am before going up to the office.  I had my headphones in&#x2026; and was just sitting when this girl comes up to me and says &#x201C;Hi! You must be Maeghan!&#x201D; I was a bit shocked&#x2026; I don&#x2019;t know anyone in Toronto&#x2026;  and thought to myself.. man I must look really awkward or something for this girl to clue in that I was new here&#x2026; but it turned out she was my supervisor for the week and had looked at my website before I got there haha.  &#xD;&#xD;We took the elevator up to the 32nd floor of the building and I got introduced to the team.  I got to my desk and I had a company manual with my name on the cover and pictures of all the executive team with word-bubbles welcoming me to BBDO. &#xD;&#xD;Right off the bat, Justine &amp; Bianca (my supervisors) showed me around the office and brought me to some of their meetings. I got to sit and listen which was valuable for the first day.  It really helped me understand the new atmosphere I was in, but always was really cool to see what these ladies job entailed. &#xD;&#xD;We got to work on two really wicked projects. &#xD;&#xD;Project A) A brand new food product to North America &#x2013; it has been very successful in the South America and Asia markets and the client wanted us to create a TV commercial to be aired in the new year. Then there was Project B) an existing popular brand that the client wanted to create a campaign TV, print, and online app to convince consumers to buy more of the product.    &#xD;&#xD;I honestly had no idea how much work out side of creative efforts went into developing campaigns. They do endless research of what else is out there, analyze how to be better, along with the goal of creating something that viewers will connect with or influence behaviour.  &#xD;&#x2028;I really value being able to job shadowing if projects are large to complete in a week.  I agree with the people who ask&#x2026; one week is a short time to learn from a company, but listening and talking with these people who enjoy what they do and know it inside out really gives a unique perspective to determine if this is an industry I am curious and wanting to learn more about.  &#xD;&#xD;Some of the work I got to do was some competitive analysis for Doritors which was interesting to see what is out there. I was pretty stoked when my research was selected to send to the clients.  I also got to look into apps, ads, and technology that is trending in the marketing sector.  &#x2028;&#xD;Its funny, after being there for two weeks I started to be more aware of advertisements around me and I automatically started analyzing them.  Like what they are trying to communicate, are they effective at influencing a behaviour or emotion, and is the ad worth winning awards.  BBDO had a TON of awards for the work they have done. Literally, every floor had shelves of award winning work.   They also had a random large hammer head made of foam that took up a whole office space&#x2026; on a more random note. :) &#xD;&#xD;Anyway, bouncing back to the creative team that was working on Project A &#x2013; they designed NINE totally different script ideas for the TV commercial to mesh with the concept the client was looking for (and I kid not.. when I see it on TV, I am going to jump up and down while saying &#x201C;I got to help with that!!&#x201D;).  I watched the ideas develop over the week and then we went with the team to pitch their scripts to the client. &#xD;&#xD;I was really interested in the creative side of the ad agency&#x2013; listening to the team come up with the ideas and watch them grow from the concept was so cool. It was like watching the ideas come to life.  &#xD;&#xD;BBDO has about 500 people in two buildings across different 5 floors of offices&#x2026;. So this was definitely the biggest company I have worked for yet!  I found it very different to be in a position and atmosphere that departmentalizes the work.  I am so used to working with a team and doing all the work to complete a project, it was interesting to see otherwise.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Something I really enjoyed at BBDO was the cool events that happened while I was there. It just really made me feel like I was a part of the team, even though it was for a short time. For example&#x2026; they were raising money for the United Way.... so they had beer and snacks circle the office ever day at 2pm.  So I could get beer and chips for $4!  I got to walk around with a cart  and meet everyone in the office.  That was pretty rad.  &#xD;&#xD;They also had different social events that employees could do to mingle and meet other people in the office. They did flip cup tournament after work and dodgeball! The dodgeball was called murder ball.. and they had little murder scenes with toys and taped areas on each floor.  The posters all over the office said things along the lines of &#x201C;have you every wanted to take out your boss? Now you can.&#x201D;  Lol  &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;The girls I worked with were absolutely awesome.  Jennifer, Justine, Kara, Bianca, Lava and Stephanie all made me feel very much as a part of the team and were so generous at sharing their knowledge of the advertising world.&#xD;&#xD;  &#xD;&#xD;It was really valuable to be able to work in a large company atmosphere, it taught me a lot about structure, working with other peoples deadlines and overall policy.  Something that I was not used to before this.  &#xD;&#xD;I really enjoyed living in Toronto.  There is just so much going on and people were so nice.  I didn&#x2019;t get to celebrate thanksgiving, so one of my close friends at home introduced me to her family who were celebrating thanksgiving the week after.  It was so nice to be able to have a conversation and enjoy others company.  I also got to meet up with a guy who works for the David Suzuki foundation and he was really rad, we went for pumpkin spiced beer, which is surprisingly VERY good. &#xD;&#xD;I am blown away by the generosity of people who support other people&#x2019;s dreams.  Its amazing, but totally true&#x2026;. if you aspire to do anything, there are people out there who will do anything they can to help you.  So I really hope that as you read this, you believe that you are truly capable of doing anything, you just have to work to get there. &#xD;&#xD;I heard a cool quote today: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;people who work hard, get lucky. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;I am so appreciative for all the people I have met and talked to along this journey so far and am beyond honoured that students and business people across Canada are sharing their stories with me and I feel so lucky to be able to share the story and crazy adventure I am on.&#xD;&#xD;I am so sorry for the delay on this.  I had the most eventful week... that you probably won&#x2019;t believe and I will be posting soon along with my San Francisco adventures. :) &#xD;&#xD;Stay awesome, and thank you again for reading.&#xD;&#xD;Maegs &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Ps. here is a tour of the office!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#x2028;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="22_Working_in_the_%28m%29AD_industry%21_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
