<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog</link>
    <description>I documented my journey every step of the way because I believe the best way to enrich my perspective is to have the opportunity to express my thoughts, reflect on all the wonderful things I am learning, share the experience, and always be grateful for all the people I meet.  :) 

connect with me here --&gt; 
     :: facebook :: twitter :: linkedin ::
</description>
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from my last #$*@ up. </title>
      <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2013/4/23_What_I_learned_from_my_last_$_%40_up..html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e98a7e22-af1f-4d98-a698-db7b8ddb8ba7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 19:14:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m young, I&#x2019;m stupid and I make mistakes. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After walking something like 30 blocks.. talking to myself and waving my hands excessively in the air (kind of like Tom Cruise in Jerry McGuire)..... I find myself sitting at &lt;a href="http://notman.org/en/"&gt;Notman House&lt;/a&gt; talking to my friend &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/zdesroches"&gt;Zoe&lt;/a&gt; - she is always so supportive.  The conclusion of our talk was unintended, but this is what I learned from my last #$(@ up... &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;ll Never Do That Again! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I can&#x2019;t even begin to describe how terrible I felt for 8 hours straight... seriously.. 8 hours.. &lt;br/&gt;Although my nerves stuck around longer then welcome... the lesson I learned was almost instant.  I can&#x2019;t change what I&#x2019;ve done, I can only do the best with what I have... and be honest moving forward.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Crash fast, build faster and let your grief go. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m Glad I Put Myself Out There And Took A Risk. God Hates A Coward. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I tried something... and it didn&#x2019;t work...... shit. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m not going say it&#x2019;s easy to be the person standing on the edge preaching that you have the answer... especially when no one asked you a question... &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But I am glad I made myself vulnerable and known as someone who cares.  I&#x2019;ll continue to search for answers and share my ideas... no matter how stupid or naive they are. I am the girl who stood up and spoke... not the one who sat back and watched. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cowards don&#x2019;t steer change... it&#x2019;s the people who are brave enough that do.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I Think I Am Smarter Then That Now &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It&#x2019;s hard to tell sometimes... but experience is a great thing. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Being able to draw from past events and apply them to other situations makes me feel like I&#x2019;m wiser than before.   I&#x2019;m able to predict potential outcomes from what I&#x2019;ve learned but also view obstacles from a different point of view. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some of the most interesting people I know say they went through years of #$%@ up&#x2019;s to get to where they are today..  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So I guess in short, I&#x2019;m a beginner.  I&#x2019;m young, stupid and make mistakes..... but it&#x2019;s ok - even the great start there too. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;___&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I don&#x2019;t think my blog is life changing or NY Times worthy.. but it&#x2019;s honest and from the heart.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;thanks for reading.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Just Maeghan &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object000.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2013/4/23_What_I_learned_from_my_last_$_%40_up..html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 things 2012 taught me. </title>
      <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2013/1/25_12_things_2012_taught_me..html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebbd3536-6866-4357-841d-ea4c93fadf9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 14:43:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 A TIGER DOESN&#x2019;T LOSE SLEEP OVER THE OPINION OF A SHEEP&lt;br/&gt;Somethings are not important. Realistically, life is a mess and nothing is fair. I have no control over the thoughts, opinions and actions of others. Yet, I still worried about upsetting or letting people down. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I think women struggle with this more than men.. but my mentor always told me.. &#x201C;Maeghan, it doesn&#x2019;t matter [what other people think]. The less you give a damn.. the happier you will be.&#x201D; It wasn&#x2019;t until this year that I fully understood worrying will never change the outcome, so don&#x2019;t lose sleep over it. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: It&#x2019;s important to listen and respect different perspectives, but you shouldn&#x2019;t compare or be controlled by the opinion of others.  Be confident in yourself and what you can do. &#x2028;&#x2028;&lt;br/&gt;11) ENVIRONMENTAL INFLUENCE &lt;br/&gt;I learned that the right environment accelerates the time and ability to produce good work; the right people in that environment enrich the thoughts I had; and, having the right reason to work produced the greatest results.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My surroundings are something I can control and have more influence over me than I realized. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Find an environment where you can solve problems creatively and execute them. You don&#x2019;t have to stay in a place you are not growing. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 NEVER WANT TO BE AVERAGE&lt;br/&gt;I have nothing against being average but believe no one should aspire or settle to be. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Why? Because you&#x2019;ll never be questioned about it!  All of a sudden, 20 years from now, you&#x2019;ll find yourself in good company with everyone who lives an unremarkably average life.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In 20 years, this is going to be a problem. I was watching a &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WMF-Z74C1QE"&gt;TEDTalk&lt;/a&gt; about how droids are going to take our jobs in the future.... 1) omg! 2) average is a dying breed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As James Altucher says, &lt;a href="http://techcrunch.com/2013/01/12/10-reasons-why-2013-will-be-the-year-you-quit-your-job/"&gt;Average is replaceable&lt;/a&gt;.. Jobs that existed 20 years ago don&#x2019;t exist today because of the technology advancements we&#x2019;ve made.  Our future in the workforce will be measured by the impact we have to change the lives of those around us. Moreover, to make our world a better place. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Be you, strive to be better and put yourself out there every chance you can. Commit yourself to constant improvement. Never settle being just ok. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 DON&#x2019;T WAIT TO FIGURE OUT WHO YOU ARE&lt;br/&gt;How long are you willing to wait before you are smart enough, strong enough, brave enough and quick enough to achieve the things you want to?&#x2028;&#x2028;Quitting my college job was one of the scariest things because I had no idea what I wanted to do post graduation... I didn&#x2019;t know what I was good at, what was out there or what I would enjoy.  However, taking action to experience a variety of different jobs and putting myself out there not only built my confidence, it gave me clarity to be the kind of person I wanted to be.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Don&#x2019;t wait to figure yourself out. Get out there and let the experience give direction to the person you want to be. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 GIVE UP ON BLAME &amp;amp; EXCUSES&lt;br/&gt;I find we have an unbelievable tolerance for blame and excuses.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This year, I started cutting people off that were doing it and asked them to take responsibility for solving the problem.  It was interesting to see the response... often they tried to continue passing the blame but the more it happened, the more I realized the time that was being wasted.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If there are constructive reasons to why something wasn&#x2019;t done or blame passed to others..  don&#x2019;t waste time complaining... use those points find to a solution. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Before complaining or making excuses - think about making a plan to how you are going to fix the problem. I hope that if I am caught - someone calls me out on it.  We are all in this together. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 MAKE DO WITH LESS&lt;br/&gt;Whenever I am stuck on a project, or trying to tackle something that isn&#x2019;t getting the support it needs - I try to act, think and execute like an underdog*. Why? Because if you are building from the ground up with the tools available, you don&#x2019;t realize what you can and can&#x2019;t do. The focus shifts from the walls around the problem to new creative solutions.  Effectively.. you just do it!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Don&#x2019;t wait for the tools that make the task easy, get started and make the best with the tools you have.  Build people, value and belief behind the cause. The rest of what you need will come... It always does. &#x2028;*lesson learned from friends at facebook. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 SPEAK NOW &lt;br/&gt;What will you do with your voice? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ask for help? Negotiate a raise? Teach others something they don&#x2019;t know? Ask for something you want?  Tell someone how much you care?  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Most people don&#x2019;t get to experience new opportunity because they are too afraid to speak up.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dan Martell wrote a &lt;a href="http://blog.clarity.fm/the-best-things-come-to-those-who-ask-entrepreneur-advice/"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; recently that sums it up well - You can&#x2019;t be afraid of looking stupid, damaging your pride, getting in trouble or asking for what you want.  There are advantages of being bold: leadership; opportunity; recognition; and, faith from others.  These are not favours that get handed out as gifts at your birthday party... they are things you grasp.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: No one else will ask/speak for you. And really... what is the worst that can happen? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 VALUE YOU &lt;br/&gt;This is probably the most important lesson our education system is overlooking.. being able to understand and evaluate one's worth. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Everything has a price tag these days, including our time and experience.  As I exited university and started pitching my plan to &#x201C;work for free&#x201D; as part of my job search... every CEO asked me.. &#x201C;What value can you bring to us&#x201D;.  At first... i had no idea... I just knew I would be grateful for the chance to try.  But what sold the pitch was understanding what value I brought to the table. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Experience, background, strengths, weaknesses, interests etc.  What would people pay to have someone like you work? Ask around. Get different opinions, and be confident in what you have to offer.  This is the only way you will know if you are growing, being valued and where you need to focus on improvement.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Knowing your worth shows confidence in your abilities, not your resume. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 STAY CONNECTED&lt;br/&gt;A wise friend once told me &#x201C;its not about your net-worth, its about your network&#x201D; and everyday that proves to be more true.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In university, I met a TON of people at different events on and off campus.. but moving across the country made me feel like as though I was starting from scratch. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Proximity does have impact however, keeping in touch is as important.  Last year, I made a list: people I look up to; people who have supported me; contacts I hope to work with in the future; and, friends/family who I care about.  &lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;I started sending updates....not necessarily facebook status updates.. but tailored messages to what was going on in the life of Maeghan.  The people who supported me responded quickly and wholeheartedly with any challenges I faced - no matter the distance.  The people who I admired acknowledged the milestones achieved over the year and suggested ways to be better. The contacts I hoped to work with in the future asked me questions as well as offered their help. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Find ways to build and maintain relationships. People are valuable no matter where you are.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 PICKUP BALL - DIVERSIFY YOUR TEAM&lt;br/&gt;I used to play competitive basketball and my coach always said be strategic in picking your team... be careful not to draft too many players with the same skills, look for a balance in experience, ego and background - this is how you build a team that wins championships. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The same concept applies to your personal &#x201C;dream team&#x201D;... ie: mentors and friends. The questions, the conversations and support you have are influenced by the people you surround yourself with.    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Be strategic and and diverse with who you want in your life. Work together as a team to achieve great things. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 BE CURIOUS &lt;br/&gt;&#x201C;I&#x2019;m bored&#x201D; is a pointless thing to say. We live in a world gifting a vast opportunity that I can assume we&#x2019;ve only seen/experienced less than 1% of.  When I&#x2019;m asked about &#x201C;dream jobs&#x201D;, extra-curricular projects or building houses in Mexico... i say I do them because I have the curiosity to find them... and just do it. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Don&#x2019;t be so critical in life and allow space to imagine, dream and try new things.  Don&#x2019;t just do it once... push yourself to be curious all the time.  Finding your passion is so 1999, curiosity is what fuels the drive to do bigger and better things.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Live outside of your job. Live great stories so you can share with others.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	HAPPINESS IS PURSUED &lt;br/&gt;If asked &#x201C;what makes you happy..&#x201D; would you hesitate to think? Or do you know?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;People often comment on how I am never not smiling.. or ask if I ever get angry.. (which I do!) but my answer is simply: I wake up every morning and know I am going to do one of the things that makes me happy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Working on projects I love; spending time with people I care about; experiencing places or things I&#x2019;ve never before; eating ice cream; and, telling stories are highlights in my life. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To me, this is the meaning of life. When I can think confidently and quickly about things I love and be creative in ways that gets me excited.. I know, with a smile I am pursuing happiness. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013 Lesson: Find what makes you happy, write it down and make time for it to happen. Happiness doesn&#x2019;t find you, you find it.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2013... I am ready to kick ass.  :) Let&#x2019;s do this. &lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;Just Maeghan &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object000_1.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2013/1/25_12_things_2012_taught_me..html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How serious is your working relationship?</title>
      <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/9/30_How_serious_is_your_working_relationship.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11dbfe21-b7ca-448e-aa63-151e086fb679</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 14:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>by &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/author/maeghan-smulders/"&gt;Maeghan Smulders&lt;/a&gt; &#x2014; September 21, 2012 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In my final year of University, the time came to start looking for a serious relationship: one where I felt loved; one where I would grow; one where I was accepted into a caring family. That&#x2019;s right&#x2014;I was looking for a great job at an amazing company. &lt;br/&gt;Like my friends, I was focusing all of my energy and effort to find this &#x201C;dream job.&#x201D; But as the interviews went on, I saw many people settling for whatever was handed to them, committing the next 2-5 years of their lives to a job they spent just &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/job-search/i-spy-how-to-scope-out-a-company-before-the-interview/"&gt;a couple of hours researching&lt;/a&gt; and interviewing with.&lt;br/&gt;I definitely didn&#x2019;t want this path, and I became increasingly determined to find the right company to build a career and relationship with.&#xA0;And that determination inspired a project that changed my life entirely. I call it&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Project_ONE12.html"&gt;ProjectONE12&lt;/a&gt;;&#xA0;a self-created initiative in which I speed-interned with 10 different companies in 112 days across North America in hopes of finding my dream job.&lt;br/&gt;The experience taught me many things, but looking back, the career lessons I am most grateful for are these.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;Confidence is Magnetic&lt;br/&gt;At the beginning of the process, when I was pitching my project to different companies, I started my conversation with something to he effect of, &#x201C;Hey, it&#x2019;s Maeghan and I would really like to intern with you because&#x2026;&#x201D;&lt;br/&gt;I was disregarded or hung up on every time. So I decided to take a different approach. With every call, I shared with pride the vision I had, the track record I had created, and the enthusiasm I had for what I was trying to accomplish.&#xA0;To my surprise, these conversations turned. I no longer had to chase companies to hire me&#x2014;instead, the companies were chasing me!&lt;br/&gt;The lesson here: &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/career/be-fearless-at-work-3-confidence-boosting-tactics/"&gt;Confidence is more memorable&lt;/a&gt; than any resume, qualification, or degree.&#xA0;Have it, and don&#x2019;t be afraid to show it.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;You Find Out What You Want (and Don&#x2019;t) by Dating Around&lt;br/&gt;Most of us put an unrealistic expectation on ourselves to have our whole lives figured out by the time we graduate from college. But really&#x2014;why? Do we expect to marry the first dude we go on a date with? (Or even start a long-term relationship with him?)&lt;br/&gt;Throughout my experience, I got to &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/job-search/why-a-winding-career-path-is-totally-ok/"&gt;spend time in many different companies&lt;/a&gt; and cultures across industries. And I got to question all kinds of things about my career: Do I want to work in a small, medium, or large company?&#xA0;Is there a difference between working for a male or female CEO? Do I want to work in a non-profit or would I rather go corporate and donate my money to a cause?&lt;br/&gt;I was able to define aspects of a career that I liked and&#xA0;understand&#xA0;which ones I didn&#x2019;t&#x2014;and this allowed me to focus my energy on where I actually wanted to be.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;You Can&#x2019;t Have a One-Sided Relationship&lt;br/&gt;So, what was biggest thing that I found out I wanted? A company that would invest in me as much as I would invest in it. I didn&#x2019;t want to waste my time in a relationship that wasn&#x2019;t willing to support my career and goals.&lt;br/&gt;I found that these one-sided relationships are all too common in the workplace&#x2014;but I also found that it&#x2019;s often because people accept the status quo. I talked with many people and was surprised at how few people fought for the things they deserved, be it compensation, a promotion, &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/career/the-secret-to-getting-more-responsibility/"&gt;more responsibility&lt;/a&gt;, training, whatever.&lt;br/&gt;What I learned is, in order to make a relationship with your job go both ways, you have to ask for it. Yes, it&#x2019;s intimidating, but the only way you&#x2019;re going to get what you deserve is by standing up for yourself and knowing your value. No one else is going to do that for you.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;Don&#x2019;t Settle&lt;br/&gt;Finally, this was the most important lesson of all. By steering clear of the jobs that felt like settling to me, I was able to learn some really special things&#x2014;not just about the kind of company I wanted to be with, but also the kind of professional I aspired to be.&lt;br/&gt;The journey to find my dream job challenged me to figure out what I wanted, to believe in the company I wanted to work for, to find the feeling of being valued, to &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/career/career-advancement-month-at-the-daily-muse/"&gt;grow in my career&lt;/a&gt;, and to strengthen my commitment to work through the ups and downs of it.&lt;br/&gt;And so, after 10 jobs, six cities, 47 job offers, and 112 days of working for free, I landed a self-created position with Beyond the Rack&#x2014;&lt;a href="http://business.financialpost.com/2011/06/24/montreals-beyond-the-rack-named-north-americas-fastest-growing-online-retailer/"&gt;named the fastest growing start-up&lt;/a&gt; in North America in 2011&#x2014;and I know that I couldn&#x2019;t be happier.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;When I started the adventure, everyone (including my family) thought I was crazy&#x2014;and I almost believed them. But&#xA0;today, I am ecstatic about my new adventures and truly believe that dream jobs do exist. And no, we just can&#x2019;t expect them to fall in our laps&#x2014;we have to go out and find them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It was August 22, 2012 that I got an email from The Daily Muse (my favourite blog) to share ProjectONE12 with their readers.  What made the email more special was the request to write was a result of people contacting them about my story.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;Its been a year since I started and 4 months since I finished. Looking back - I could have never anticipated this.  But looking forward, I&#x2019;m beyond grateful for every single day. &lt;br/&gt;check out the daily muse/see the original post &lt;a href="http://www.thedailymuse.com/job-search/10-jobs-in-112-days-my-speed-interning-experience/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object000_2.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/9/30_How_serious_is_your_working_relationship.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grow up? </title>
      <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/7/15_Grow_up._But_live_in_Neverland..html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">965361d9-9135-41db-be6a-535083c4dfec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2012 15:01:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>I remember being 15 years old telling my friends that by the time I turned 25, I would be living in California, on a beach, with a dog, a porsche and be married to Justin Timberlake with out a doubt in my mind.  It seemed possible - I mean, I had 10 years to make it happen!!!  So you can imagine my massive disappointment and quarter life crisis that occurred when I turned 21 and realized that the life I had pictured wasn&#x2019;t going to happen (The closest I have been to Justin Timberlake was in concert and although he looked directly at me... I couldn&#x2019;t tell if the connection was love at first sight or the feeling of nausea from the flashing lights). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I am still marginally depressed that I am not married to Mr. JT on the year of my 25th bday... but at the same time, I don&#x2019;t share the same undying love for him as I did when I was fifteen (which might change if he makes a new album someday soon..... hint hint Justin... ;D ) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The reality is, we change.  It is totally normal not to love the same things you did as a kid.  My parents call this..... &#x201C;growing up&#x201D;. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What I find interesting with growing up is that the more we age, the less we act like kids. I know you may be thinking... well yes, its not appropriate to behave like a child when you have responsibility or know better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sure, that is what our mature self is telling us.. but I see three problems with it:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 We lose excitement for life &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My neighbours from Calgary came with their two kids to Montreal this week and I volunteered to babysit them for a few hours. When I got to their hotel, I asked the kids if they wanted to go to a water fountain....  Well.. between the two of them, I got a 20 min rant response about their swim suits, love for bringing their toys - more specifically their trains into the water and how much they loved water fountains. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I just sat back and laughed - Ryan (the younger one..) was so excited about going that he spoke too quickly and could only announce every second or third word that came out of his mouth and left the rest to mumbling.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As an adult... have you ever had a moment like that? SO excited to share the world as you see with others?  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the last few months, I have been meeting and chatting with a lot of different people - small talk and business related.  It blows my mind how almost all conversations I have are routine.... no matter the setting.  &#x201C;How is work?&#x201D; &#x201C;What do you do?&#x201D; &#x201C;How is the family?&#x201D; &#x201C;How was the weekend?&#x201D;  etc...  with maybe one or two other personal questions tossed in there. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I don&#x2019;t know about you.. but discussions like this can get boring!  Now, I don&#x2019;t expect to have a conversation about water fountains with everyone.... but after spending the evening with Ryan &amp;amp; Oliver.. I wondered what happened to our courage and excitement to share stories of things that we enjoy, or the conversation of random details/events that happened through out the day. You know, the little things in life, not necessarily the routine things... &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Last week I had an epic fail trying to wash my car (it involves me leaving my windows open and being just soaked by the machine and the old lady behind me waiting 20 min to wash her car because I had no idea how to make the machine work.. )  Although no one has specifically asked me &#x201C;Hey Maeghan, did you wash your car this week?&#x201D;, I am asked quite often about how I am liking Montreal, or how my weekends are.  So I have taken it upon my own accord to steer the conversation and share the world as I see it.  Something I have notice about doing this is that it brings a smile to the listeners face, a sense of trust and perspective that wasn&#x2019;t there before and the listener remembers what we talked about and often shares the story with others.  Now I see how beneficial it is to be thrilled about what you love, or the things you do. It has impact and substance that stands out in a crowd and makes you, you. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Don&#x2019;t loose your excitement - life is collection of moments, not things. It may seem irrelevant or &#x201C;childish&#x201D; to notice and appreciate random details.. but it is a perspective in your life that is unique to you.  Share it with others and you will be surprised at impression it leaves. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2) We lose our ability to grow and be better&lt;br/&gt;My second week in Montreal was a tough one.  I have been living on the road for the greater portion of 2 years, but coming to Montreal is my first time moving out of my home in Calgary and officially living on my own.  If you don&#x2019;t know this about me, I am ridiculous and put a lot of pressure on myself and have an even higher expectation to do good things (work or personally related).  But in my 2nd week here, I was still learning and gathering information about my job (I expected to be making millions of dollars in just 8 days... so I was anxious to why it was taking me so long.. haha ridiculous expectations point and example), I didn&#x2019;t have any friends or family here so my evenings and weekends were spent alone in my apartment or walking around the streets and finally, I had no committed responsibility (Back in Calgary, I was volunteering, meeting people, working and doing school so my days were packed full... this is the first time in 4 years that I had absolutely nothing to do).  &lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;The tipping point of this lesson was on my 2nd Sunday here, I was walking in Montreal when a homeless man chased and pushed me on the street.  It scared the living daylights out of me and no one around did anything to help.... I was completely alone with a crowd watching. The thought terrified me to the effect that thunderstorms or monsters scare children - I didn&#x2019;t know how I was going to move on without my family around and needed them to tell me everything was going to be alright.   I got back to my apartment crying and couldn&#x2019;t sleep that night. Monday came and I asked my boss that If I died, would anyone notice or come to find me? I don&#x2019;t think this is a question many people ask themselves..&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;I was so scared, lost and overwhelmed with my responsibility to be an adult and grow up.. that I was on the edge of quitting my new job, packing my bags and heading home to Calgary.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After work that day, I called my mentor and had an emotional break down... I hadn&#x2019;t felt that terrible about anything in a really long time.  He calmed me down and told me that these feelings and thoughts were natural... so I took his words to digest and went for a walk to clear my mind.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I was thinking for hours on how I reacted and as time went by, started to think about ways I could prevent the fear from happening again.  I didn&#x2019;t have the security blanket of my family... but I made it a priority to talk with people, text all the time, hang out and make new friends.  I even made a point to take some time off and volunteer to meet local people which helped wonders. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At first, I was embarrassed by this.  An adult crying like a baby because she was scared and missed home. But the more I talked to people trying to solve my problem.. the more I realized that very few actually ask for help when they need a hand.. and an even smaller amount work towards anything that has risk or hardship associated with it.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now, I would never wish hardship, fear or challenges to anyone... but this is a lesson that really surprised me. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We have this idea that as adults.. we should have our shit together and not go out looking for trouble.  But in retrospect of my time here, I&#x2019;ve grown so much by facing these struggles on my own... even though I already considered myself an adult... i guess there is always more room to grow. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As a kid we have the excuse to crawl in to mom and dads bed and hide under the covers till the moment passes.. but as an adult we shouldn&#x2019;t be ashamed of those feelings, we just have to deal with it differently.  I know I have the ability to be courageous, find solutions, talk to people and turn that fear into an opportunity to grow and be better. That is a pretty big lesson to learn.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Don&#x2019;t be afraid of your childish emotions... love, fear, excitement etc.. they can be a bit over dramatic.. but paired with the wisdom of an adult we can grow from them and learn to be better.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	We stop dreaming..&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I love watching kids play make-believe, imagine they are in some magical place, play games with their imaginary friends or boldly state that they are going to grow up and be an astronaut, rock star, fireman or Justin Timberlake&#x2019;s wife.. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I said it before..... dreams/priorities changes as we grow old but what&#x2019;s sad is that with age dreams stop to flow as freely.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We focus our lives around the responsibility we have oppose to finding a balance and making the space to dream and pursue crazy things.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Its not as easy to chase what we desire when responsibility, relationships and family fill our thoughts, but there is something about actively working towards our goals that satisfies us in life - no matter our age. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Work hard to find balance and make time to dream.  I believe its so important!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Peter Pan is my favourite movie.. I always thought that growing up was a trap and that I would stop loving life the day I got old (Old used to be the age of 30....)  But today... I see it differently.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Growing up gives me the tools to pursue the things I want to achieve in life. I am brave, more knowledgable, able to solve my own problems and fund the things I want to. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But living in Neverland opens my mind to a greater world of possibility.  I don&#x2019;t think my ideas are stupid, my moments in life are silly or my excitement to try new things is irrelevant. Being child at heart and adult in mind gives me the chance to create a new world and flourish in it. &lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;These thoughts have helped me in Montreal.  Not only in meeting people, but in having impact and being ok with the fact that it can be scary on your own.  I hope you realize that age is just a number.. but youth lives in us forever. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some people are old at 18 and some are young at 90... time is a concept that humans created.  &#x2028;  - Yuko Ono&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Much&amp;lt;3 &#x2028;Just Maeghan &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I dedicate this post to Chris Arsenault &amp;amp; Zoe Desroches --the two Montreal'ers who got me through my 2nd week here. :) I appreciate you. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Here are pictures from my new adventure in Montreal:  &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10151038027951385.457078.504426384&amp;type=1"&gt;new life. the way i see it. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object001.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/7/15_Grow_up._But_live_in_Neverland..html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>one project ends. another one begins.</title>
      <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/5/28_one_project_ends._another_one_begins..html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fee99d93-3d57-4f6c-82ec-48d4686e5494</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 12:57:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>10 jobs + 8 months + 6 cities = 1 very exciting decision. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First I would like to say how grateful I am for the opportunity to visit, learn, work, meet and be apart of some truly amazing teams and organizations.  A HUGE thank you to all the &lt;a href="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/The_10_Companies.html"&gt;companies&lt;/a&gt; and simply wonderful people I&#x2019;ve met along the way.  You&#x2019;ve made this experience something special and I will be sure to pay forward the kindness/knowledge you shared with me, to others. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I would also like to thank all the &lt;a href="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Sponsors.html"&gt;sponsors&lt;/a&gt;, readers &amp;amp; students who have followed, listened &amp;amp; shared my story.  Seriously, you gave me the courage to stick with it - no matter the challenge.  Thank you for being apart of this too :)  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It&#x2019;s always sad to end something.... but as one project ends, the next one begins.  I&#x2019;m excited to share with you that I have accepted a position with &lt;a href="http://www.beyondtherack.com/"&gt;Beyond The Rack&lt;/a&gt; (BTR) in Montreal, Quebec starting in June.  BTR is a Canadian startup with offices in Montreal, New York as well as Las Vegas and was named the fastest growing E-tailer in the US (in 2011) by Internet Retailer Magazine.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My role with them is to manage and start a new department within the company that focuses on marketing &amp;amp; new business opportunities. :) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m stoked! Its going to be a lot of work, a new adventure and by far a wicked opportunity to learn loads.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My next challenge? Well, that is packing, moving and starting something new.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;ProjectONE12 has been the ultimate adventure and given me an invaluable education that I hope to continue to share with others. &#xA0;I hope that my journey brings attention to the fact that things have changed since our parents went to school and got jobs. The world is full of opportunity and we should be curious, be bold, ask questions and pursue with enthusiasm the things we want to.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No matter how crazy the idea... make things happen. :) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So that is it for me! Well... for now anyways. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wish me luck on the next adventure and thank you again for your interest, support &amp;amp; kind words.  I appreciate you. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Just Maeghan &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object002.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/5/28_one_project_ends._another_one_begins..html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping tabs on life. </title>
      <link>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/5/18_Keeping_tabs_on_life..html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3e86cfd-f4af-40c3-a129-0ac6af925bdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 17:20:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Do you keep a track record of your life?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You know, taken the time to connect the dots to why you are the way you are?  Considered everything from the opportunities you took, the mistakes you made, the people you met or the inspiration you found to becoming who you are today?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Maybe I have too much spare time... but I do that.  It reminds me of moments and lessons I&#x2019;ve already learned, that I sometimes seem to forget. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The worst is, I am most forgetful of these lessons when put in a position of making a decision outside of my comfort zone... terrible time to be tripping right?! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So since I&#x2019;m in the head space of reflecting... Here are 5/100+ lessons I learned in my race with life:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;5) It&#x2019;s because I&#x2019;m homeschooled.. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For those who know me, that is my answer to all the ridiculous things I do. One: because it&#x2019;s true. Two: because it taught me to have confidence in making mistakes. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I used to do stupid things all the time.  I have run in to walls, asked dumb questions and said ridiculous things in front of large amounts of people - but that&#x2019;s not the stupid part. What is stupid is that I would justify why I did them to other people! In fact, It was so stupid of me that I almost stopped trying new things because I was so afraid of screwing up or what others would think of me.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It wasn&#x2019;t until university that I realized I didn&#x2019;t have to say or prove anything. I make mistakes to learn and the day I stop making them is the day I stop learning.  Believe me when I say, I picked up pretty quick not to text while running. Or how to be successful by asking better questions and how I should be more specific when pitching ideas to gain support or results. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I learned that all I have to say when I make a mistake is that &#x201C;I was homeschooled&#x201D;.  It usually gets a laugh and I don&#x2019;t have to say anything else beyond that. Why focus on the mistake in the past, when you can focus on the results and prevent them in the future. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lesson: You don&#x2019;t have to prove yourself to anyone. Be you, make mistakes &amp;amp; stay awesome. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 Be Curious &lt;br/&gt;When I was 7 years old, I wanted to grow up and be Pochohauntas.  I would run around the backyard in my bare feet, with a towel and paint my dog to look more like a raccoon as I reenacted the adventures of the Disney character.  I wasn&#x2019;t just pretending to be Pochohauntas at the time, I was reading books about her and would go to Heritage Park to learn more about the settlers and natives that shared the land before I got here.  I wanted to learn everything about her, so I could understand what it took to BE her!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Although I never did grow up to be Pochohauntas (as I realized that job was taken..) I shared my interest with every person I met to ensure they knew how cool she really was to me.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I did this because I was curious and eager to learn.  No one made me read the book, tell me to watch the movie or have me write a test on it..... I  did it because I wanted to know more. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m sure you are like.. oh yes.. all kids do that.  True - but don&#x2019;t let curiosity stop there. I grew out of Disney Princess stories.. but I carried the desire to learn with me when I wanted to become the best horse jumper. The smartest marine biologist. The most athletic basketball player. The best mortgage broker. The best exchange student in China. An award winning Project Leader. A Honours receiving University student.... I have been so lucky to do many things.. but the point I am trying to make is, you should never deny yourself the opportunity to be curious and strive to be the best at something new.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Curiosity inspires growth. education. excitement and the opportunity for you to find a passion you might not have known you had. :) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lesson: Be curious. Commit to new things. And if you realize it&#x2019;s not for you... look at it as an experience that pushed you in a new direction.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 Collect moments and not things!! &lt;br/&gt;I started working for a mortgage company when I was 14 years old.  Something I learned quick is that more people will tell you when you are wrong than when you are right and as a kid.. I took that very emotionally. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I started to journal my positive thoughts and moments to try and keep my spirits up.  Anytime I did something that I was proud of (regardless of what other people would think).... i would write about that moment in a journal.  I wrote about people I met, problems I solved and random things that made me happy... and I did for 2 years.  The cool thing was.. looking back, I had a great collection of special moments that outweighed the bad!  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lesson: Cherish your special moments, achievements and thoughts.  No one knows the value of them except you - so treasure them. Material things become old.. thoughts live forever. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 Kiss &amp;amp; Tell&lt;br/&gt;I learned this lesson in a way I hope no one else has to. I was put into a situation where the idea that I might not see my family again was very real.   And let me tell you... living through a shooting was one of the scariest moments of my life. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ever since that day, I continue to tell my parents, my two younger sisters and my older brother that I love them. I go and see my grandparents as often as I can.  I tell my friends that I appreciate them.. and thank my mentors and coworkers for taking the time to helping me learn and become better.   I thank people often and I thank them with all my heart. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Remember this... Although you love your family and friends, or throughly enjoy the people you meet or work with... they have no way of knowing how you feel unless you tell them.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lesson: Life is too short. Kiss, tell &amp;amp; be thankful with all your heart. The people in your life are what makes it beautiful. Don&#x2019;t let a day go by without reminding yourself and them of that. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	1)	 Punch Fear In the Face &lt;br/&gt;Fear is an illusion that we create.  We also have a phenomenally ability to create excuses that fuel illusions and give the perception that they are more difficult, more overwhelming or more impossible than they really is.  I know my excuses... &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#x201C;I don&#x2019;t have the time...&#x201D; &lt;br/&gt;&#x201C;I&#x2019;m not really talented or good at it....&#x201D;&lt;br/&gt;&#x201C;I don&#x2019;t know where to start...&#x201D; or&lt;br/&gt;&#x201C;What would other people think... &#x201D; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now, I can only speak from my own experience on this... but the most rewarding achievements, goals, and ideas I&#x2019;ve had are a result of facing fear and metaphorically punching it in the face. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;One of my more recent run ins with fear was quitting my job at the mortgage company.   I had been employed there for 10 years and enjoyed my job. It was good job,  It paid well and I was good at it. But when graduation from university came.. I had this idea that I wanted to find my dream job.. I knew it was time for to grow up and try something new... but actually walking out the door of my job was one of the hardest things I have ever done. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You can ask my boss... I cried outrageously as I left my stapler, my pens, my security, my routine and walked into ProjectONE12... this stupid idea I had NO way of knowing whether or not it would work.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But if I hadn&#x2019;t have face that fear... I would never have been able to experiences the amazing adventures I can reflect on today. :) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lesson: Facing your fear is hard. But the reward is beyond worth it.  Don&#x2019;t cut yourself short with excuses... you never know what you are capable of until you force yourself to try.  It may not happen in a day, in a week or in a year.. but if you stick with it... when it does happen... that moment will change you and give you the opportunity to look back and not wished you had.. but proudly say... &#x201C;heck yes, I did!&#x201D;. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These are popular lessons that I am sure you have heard before.  But the way I learned them was through my own experience... and I can only imagine the ones you have learned through yours.  Reflect on them and use them.. I bet we are smarter than we give ourselves credit for. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;__________&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On a ProjectONE12 note... I&#x2019;m making some big decisions this week - picking a job, sticking to my vision and learning new things. :)  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you again for the support, excitement and enthusiasm to see where I end up. I&#x2019;m grateful for it! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- Just Maeghan &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object004.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog/Entries/2012/5/18_Keeping_tabs_on_life..html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>6</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
