<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120519" date="2012-05-19 22:13:16 -0600"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Keeping tabs on life. &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, May 18, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Do you keep a track record of your life?&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;You know, taken the time to connect the dots to why you are the way you are?  Considered everything from the opportunities you took, the mistakes you made, the people you met or the inspiration you found to becoming who you are today?&#xD;&#xD;Maybe I have too much spare time... but I do that.  It reminds me of moments and lessons I&#x2019;ve already learned, that I sometimes seem to forget. &#xD;&#xD;The worst is, I am most forgetful of these lessons when put in a position of making a decision outside of my comfort zone... terrible time to be tripping right?! &#xD;&#xD;So since I&#x2019;m in the head space of reflecting... Here are 5/100+ lessons I learned in my race with life:&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;5) It&#x2019;s because I&#x2019;m homeschooled.. &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;For those who know me, that is my answer to all the ridiculous things I do. One: because it&#x2019;s true. Two: because it taught me to have confidence in making mistakes. &#xD;&#xD;I used to do stupid things all the time.  I have run in to walls, asked dumb questions and said ridiculous things in front of large amounts of people - but that&#x2019;s not the stupid part. What is stupid is that I would justify why I did them to other people! In fact, It was so stupid of me that I almost stopped trying new things because I was so afraid of screwing up or what others would think of me.&#xD;&#xD;It wasn&#x2019;t until university that I realized I didn&#x2019;t have to say or prove anything. I make mistakes to learn and the day I stop making them is the day I stop learning.  Believe me when I say, I picked up pretty quick not to text while running. Or how to be successful by asking better questions and how I should be more specific when pitching ideas to gain support or results. &#xD;&#xD;I learned that all I have to say when I make a mistake is that &#x201C;I was homeschooled&#x201D;.  It usually gets a laugh and I don&#x2019;t have to say anything else beyond that. Why focus on the mistake in the past, when you can focus on the results and prevent them in the future. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: You don&#x2019;t have to prove yourself to anyone. Be you, make mistakes &amp; stay awesome. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 Be Curious &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;When I was 7 years old, I wanted to grow up and be Pochohauntas.  I would run around the backyard in my bare feet, with a towel and paint my dog to look more like a raccoon as I reenacted the adventures of the Disney character.  I wasn&#x2019;t just pretending to be Pochohauntas at the time, I was reading books about her and would go to Heritage Park to learn more about the settlers and natives that shared the land before I got here.  I wanted to learn everything about her, so I could understand what it took to BE her!&#xD;&#xD;Although I never did grow up to be Pochohauntas (as I realized that job was taken..) I shared my interest with every person I met to ensure they knew how cool she really was to me.  &#xD;&#xD;I did this because I was curious and eager to learn.  No one made me read the book, tell me to watch the movie or have me write a test on it..... I  did it because I wanted to know more. &#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;m sure you are like.. oh yes.. all kids do that.  True - but don&#x2019;t let curiosity stop there. I grew out of Disney Princess stories.. but I carried the desire to learn with me when I wanted to become the best horse jumper. The smartest marine biologist. The most athletic basketball player. The best mortgage broker. The best exchange student in China. An award winning Project Leader. A Honours receiving University student.... I have been so lucky to do many things.. but the point I am trying to make is, you should never deny yourself the opportunity to be curious and strive to be the best at something new.   &#xD;&#xD;Curiosity inspires growth. education. excitement and the opportunity for you to find a passion you might not have known you had. :) &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: Be curious. Commit to new things. And if you realize it&#x2019;s not for you... look at it as an experience that pushed you in a new direction.  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 Collect moments and not things!! &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I started working for a mortgage company when I was 14 years old.  Something I learned quick is that more people will tell you when you are wrong than when you are right and as a kid.. I took that very emotionally. &#xD;&#xD;I started to journal my positive thoughts and moments to try and keep my spirits up.  Anytime I did something that I was proud of (regardless of what other people would think).... i would write about that moment in a journal.  I wrote about people I met, problems I solved and random things that made me happy... and I did for 2 years.  The cool thing was.. looking back, I had a great collection of special moments that outweighed the bad!  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Lesson:&lt;/b&gt; Cherish your special moments, achievements and thoughts.  No one knows the value of them except you - so treasure them. Material things become old.. thoughts live forever. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 Kiss &amp; Tell&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I learned this lesson in a way I hope no one else has to. I was put into a situation where the idea that I might not see my family again was very real.   And let me tell you... living through a shooting was one of the scariest moments of my life. &#xD;&#xD;Ever since that day, I continue to tell my parents, my two younger sisters and my older brother that I love them. I go and see my grandparents as often as I can.  I tell my friends that I appreciate them.. and thank my mentors and coworkers for taking the time to helping me learn and become better.   I thank people often and I thank them with all my heart. &#xD;&#xD;Remember this... Although you love your family and friends, or throughly enjoy the people you meet or work with... they have no way of knowing how you feel unless you tell them.  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Lesson: &lt;/b&gt;Life is too short. Kiss, tell &amp; be thankful with all your heart. The people in your life are what makes it beautiful. Don&#x2019;t let a day go by without reminding yourself and them of that. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;	1)	 Punch Fear In the Face &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Fear is an illusion that we create.  We also have a phenomenally ability to create excuses that fuel illusions and give the perception that they are more difficult, more overwhelming or more impossible than they really is.  I know my excuses... &#xD;&#xD;&#x201C;I don&#x2019;t have the time...&#x201D; &#xD;&#x201C;I&#x2019;m not really talented or good at it....&#x201D;&#xD;&#x201C;I don&#x2019;t know where to start...&#x201D; or&#xD;&#x201C;What would other people think... &#x201D; &#xD;&#xD;Now, I can only speak from my own experience on this... but the most rewarding achievements, goals, and ideas I&#x2019;ve had are a result of facing fear and metaphorically punching it in the face. &#xD;&#xD;One of my more recent run ins with fear was quitting my job at the mortgage company.   I had been employed there for 10 years and enjoyed my job. It was good job,  It paid well and I was good at it. But when graduation from university came.. I had this idea that I wanted to find my dream job.. I knew it was time for to grow up and try something new... but actually walking out the door of my job was one of the hardest things I have ever done. &#xD;&#xD;You can ask my boss... I cried outrageously as I left my stapler, my pens, my security, my routine and walked into ProjectONE12... this stupid idea I had NO way of knowing whether or not it would work.&#xD;&#xD;But if I hadn&#x2019;t have face that fear... I would never have been able to experiences the amazing adventures I can reflect on today. :) &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Lesson&lt;/b&gt;: Facing your fear is hard. But the reward is beyond worth it.  Don&#x2019;t cut yourself short with excuses... you never know what you are capable of until you force yourself to try.  It may not happen in a day, in a week or in a year.. but if you stick with it... when it does happen... that moment will change you and give you the opportunity to look back and not wished you had.. but proudly say... &#x201C;heck yes, I did!&#x201D;. &#xD;&#xD;These are popular lessons that I am sure you have heard before.  But the way I learned them was through my own experience... and I can only imagine the ones you have learned through yours.  Reflect on them and use them.. I bet we are smarter than we give ourselves credit for. &#xD;&#xD;__________&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;On a ProjectONE12 note... I&#x2019;m making some big decisions this week - picking a job, sticking to my vision and learning new things. :)  &#xD;&#xD;Thank you again for the support, excitement and enthusiasm to see where I end up. I&#x2019;m grateful for it! &#xD;&#xD;- Just Maeghan &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="18_Keeping_tabs_on_life._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
