<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120528" date="2012-05-28 08:11:07 -0600"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;one project ends. another one begins.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, May 28, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;10 jobs + 8 months + 6 cities = 1 very exciting decision. &#xD;&#xD;First I would like to say how grateful I am for the opportunity to visit, learn, work, meet and be apart of some truly amazing teams and organizations.  A HUGE thank you to all the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/The_10_Companies.html"&gt;companies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; and simply wonderful people I&#x2019;ve met along the way.  You&#x2019;ve made this experience something special and I will be sure to pay forward the kindness/knowledge you shared with me, to others. &#xD;&#xD;I would also like to thank all the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.maeghansmulders.com/Maeghan/Sponsors.html"&gt;sponsors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;, readers &amp; students who have followed, listened &amp; shared my story.  Seriously, you gave me the courage to stick with it - no matter the challenge.  Thank you for being apart of this too :)  &#xD;&#xD;It&#x2019;s always sad to end something.... but as one project ends, the next one begins.  I&#x2019;m excited to share with you that I have accepted a position with &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.beyondtherack.com"&gt;Beyond The Rack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; (BTR) in Montreal, Quebec starting in June.  BTR is a Canadian startup with offices in Montreal, New York as well as Las Vegas and was named the fastest growing E-tailer in the US (in 2011) by Internet Retailer Magazine.&#xD;&#xD;My role with them is to manage and start a new department within the company that focuses on marketing &amp; new business opportunities. :) &#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;m stoked! Its going to be a lot of work, a new adventure and by far a wicked opportunity to learn loads.&#xD;&#xD;My next challenge? Well, that is packing, moving and starting something new.  &#xD;&#xD;ProjectONE12 has been the ultimate adventure and given me an invaluable education that I hope to continue to share with others. &#xA0;I hope that my journey brings attention to the fact that things have changed since our parents went to school and got jobs. The world is full of opportunity and we should be curious, be bold, ask questions and pursue with enthusiasm the things we want to.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;No matter how crazy the idea... make things happen. :) &#xD;&#xD;So that is it for me! Well... for now anyways. &#xD;&#xD;Wish me luck on the next adventure and thank you again for your interest, support &amp; kind words.  I appreciate you. &#xD;&#xD;Just Maeghan &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="28_one_project_ends._another_one_begins._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="692px" height="458px"/>
</content>
