<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120103" date="2012-01-03 18:58:43 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;And they say - wheres your head at?&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, January 3, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;I think its funny that I have experienced 8 &#x201C;first-day&#x201D;s of work in the last 3 months, yet for some reason.... I still get incredibly nervous when Monday&#x2019;s come. &#xD;&#xD;The new year has brought me to Toronto where I will be working in my last 3 jobs to reach the goal of 10 by January 20th.  I am still trying to process all of the knowledge, information and perspective that I have gained over the last few months and during the holidays, I was able to create a plan with how I hope to finish the project as well as, what adventure I hope to embark on next.&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;I have determined my pursuit for a &#x201C;dream career&#x201D; is in the technology sector based on several reasons: &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	1)	I love problem solving or the idea of taking something and making it better&#xD;	2)	The vast reach and opportunity to help others across industries&#xD;	3)	The overall pace and speed of work (believe me.. industries/companies move differently!) &#xD;	4)	Having a creative outlet and ability to bring ideas to life &#xD;	5)	There is never a line up for the girls washroom...&#xD;	6)	Room for growth and experimentation  &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;	7)	I am beyond fascinated by the companies and people I have met in the space. I just really want to be a part of it and contribute some enthusiasm and respect to what they do. &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;Took me 7 jobs to figure that out but my list seriously goes on and on!! If nothing else happens on this endeavour, I accomplished the goal I set for myself back in September to figure out where I wanted to go.  It is truly a special feeling to have some direction, and excitement in finding a career, in my final semester.. I was dreading it! I really wish all students could feel this as they graduate, but there is a seriously flaw in our academic system (that is a rant and problem I will save for another post or short novel, I have a goal to fix that flaw one day).  &#xD;&#xD;I just really see value in being able to pursue things that interest you because if you want to learn more, you naturally excel and push yourself to better.  You bring your own enthusiasm, and drive to the work you produce and amazing things can come from that.  &#xD;&#xD;For my last 3 jobs focused on tech, I am working in a startup, a medium sized and large company to better understand their differences.  For 10 years, I worked at a mortgage company and watched it grow from 3 employes to 10 - but now its an opportunity to apply a new perspective and figure out where I hope to work next. &#xD;&#xD;I am really excited, really nervous... I feel a lot of pressure in the coming weeks (I mean..  I put a lot of it on myself..) but its my life and career on the line... and I am scared to what might happen next.  &#xD;&#xD;Fear seems to be a best friend of mine since I started the project, especially when things get difficult.  But one of the most powerful things I learned back in school was even if I fail.. don&#x2019;t pass a class, try out for something and don&#x2019;t make the cut, told no, or simply feel afraid of a challenge... I can always get up, try again, and ask for help.  Always.   &#xD;&#xD;Steve Jobs said this that I love:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&#x2028;&#x201C;Your time is limited so don&#x2019;t waste it living someone else&#x2019;s life. Don&#x2019;t be trapped by dogma -  which is living with the results of other people&#x2019;s thinking.  Don&#x2019;t let the noise of others&#x2019; opinions drown out your inner voice. And most important, have the courage to follow your heart and intuition.  They some how already know what you truly want to become.&#x201D; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;Big goals planned for 2012 - I feel so blessed, grateful and honoured for an amazing adventure and year.   I know life is what you make it... so &#x201C;hi-five&#x201D; to making 2012 right. &#xD;&#xD;Thank you for reading and sending love - I wish you wicked awesome new year!&#xD;&#xD;Just Maeghan &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;ps. you can check out all my pictures from the adventure on my&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Maeghan-Smulders/169431223148626"&gt; facebook page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="3_And_they_say_-_wheres_your_head_at_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
