<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20111120" date="2011-11-20 23:06:45 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Taking care of business &amp; giving back. &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, November 20, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Hey hey!&#xD;&#xD;So today is a pretty special day, it marks my halfway point of ProjectONE. Five jobs down, five more to go!!  Some truly amazing things have happened thus far, and I just want to thank you again for reading and sharing your words, thoughts and inspirations with me throughout this journey.  I am beyond excited to hear that other students are wanting to pursue a similar project to mine and I am so grateful for the stories!! Thank you so much for sharing!!!! :) &#xD;&#xD;Job number 5: Working with the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tricofoundation.ca/"&gt;Trico Charitable Foundation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; in Calgary. The reason why I wanted to work with them was because during my time in University, I really enjoyed creating programs to help others within the community. Ever since I was little, my parents had my siblings and I involved in areas of charity and volunteering (as a part of our homeschooling every week). I know that giving back will always be an important aspect of my life and I wanted to find a job during the project that focused on helping others more directly.   &#xD;&#xD;With that said, I had the opportunity to speak at the launch of the Trico Foundation back in March and was stoked to work with them as their focus is supporting Social Entrepreneurship, Social Enterprise, and was created by a couple that I really admire - Wayne and Eleanor Chiu: who have a successful business, while maintaining an influence within the community of Calgary through their generous actions. &#xD;&#xD;My job for the week was to help with the preparation of the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tricofoundation.ca/social_enter.php"&gt;Enterprising Spirit: Creating Value and Social Good&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; Conference. It was quite different then my previous jobs because the companies in the past typically have a desk and outlined work for me to complete after an introduction to what they do.   But the Trico Foundation has 2 employees who run all their programs, grants and events so they needed my help to get things finalized for the conference.  I was totally ok with that because I know when planning big events, its nice to have someone there to focus on that. &#xD;&#xD;The day before the conference came around, and we had a VIP dinner at the Ranchmen&#x2019;s club with some really special individuals within the business community of Calgary, and the social enterprise industry across Canada. &#xD;&#xD;What I really enjoyed about dinner was the open table discussion on Social Enterprise and how we can better support people who are creating busineses that serve a social good in the community. &#xD;&#xD;Let me tell you... it was simply inspiring to talk with these individuals who all had different experience and involvement with the topic.  The buzz from the room got me even more excited to what the discussion would bring the following day at the conference.  We were anticipating over 150 people for the first ever, Social Enterprise Awards which is a fantastic turn out that I was excited to be a part of. &#xD;&#xD;The next morning was an early one... we had to bring all the swag bags for the guests and get all the final touches ready to go for the conference.  A cool thing about these bags was they were supplied from a social enterprise in Vancouver who sewed them from recycled Olympic flag material!!  &#xD;&#xD;Once the conference got started, people from across the city came together to learn and share their support of social enterprise.  They had guest speakers and panel discussions that I learned a lot from, but my favourite portion of the day was at the closing awards ceremony when three truly amazing individuals were recognized for their businesses, and the impact they had created within the community. &#xD;&#xD;My job during the ceremony was the tech person who used videos to announce the winners... and to be honest.. being a tech person is one of the most stressful jobs!!!! I have done it before during my time with SIFE and its seriously intense... because if any visuals look bad, I am the person to blame for making everyone else look bad... so I definitely put ALOT of pressure on myself! &#xD;&#xD;But as time came to announce the winner..... I was so happy to meet and hear the stories of three well deserving companies who are making a significant difference in their community. &#xD;&#xD;The winners were: &#x2028;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.potluckcatering.org/"&gt;Potluck Catering &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&lt;a href="http://www.mission-possible.ca/"&gt;Mission Possible&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&lt;a href="http://www.groupeconvexpr.ca/"&gt;Groupe Convex&lt;/a&gt; &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;It was such a special night.  The honourable Mayor Naheed Nenshi came to the event and shared some inspiring insight on how he wants citizens to help make the city of Calgary, my hometown, a &#x201C;better&#x201D; place.  He also turned to the audience to answer any questions or reflect on the events through out the day.  And being me... with so many wonderful things to say about the event.. I stood up and shared how the day was heart lifting and special to be a part of.  When I finished... Naheed embarrassed me a bit and told the room I was recognized for my Social Entrepreneurship at an international level and that I was being modest of my efforts.  But at that moment, I was smiling and so grateful, to be a part of something that I strongly believe in and to be even recognized for efforts that I think are minimal in comparison to these powerhouse people who are doing some amazing social based things. &#xD;&#xD;The conference ended wonderfully and I was excited to reflect and share the experience.  On Friday, the two staff members were working remotely, so I had the opportunity to help out with the development of some of their marketing materials and posters for the coming year, as well as helped with some brainstorming on the use of educational dollars allocated towards the Foundation.   &#xD;&#xD;I feel very lucky to have been apart of event.  The women I was working with at the Trico Foundation were wonderful and I am grateful for the time they spent with me.  &#xD;&#xD;The weekend rolled around, and Calgary decided to snow and reach temperatures of -25... I took that as a hint to leave quickly to Vancouver and get settled in before for my next job at ImageX starting tomorrow! &#xD; &#xD;Travelling for work in a suit case is much more tiring and uncomfortable than I had originally thought, especially when you are on a tight budget.  But I have arrived safe and sound and am looking forward to a new week of work and of course, the next adventure.  &#xD;&#xD;Thanks again for reading! Hope your day is well and can&#x2019;t wait to share more updates of an exciting week I have planned here in Vancouver!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Lots of love, &#xD;&#x2028;Just Maeghan. &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="20_I_ment.._to..._or..._Get_a_Mentor%21_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
