<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20111129" date="2011-11-29 01:26:51 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Laughing too much at work. &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, November 28, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;My time at ImageX went by VERY quickly... I think that is because there was a lot of laughing, learning and foosball :)  The job for the week was to help with some research and marketing efforts for the company, but a major portion of time was on answering the question &#x201C;why is ImageX a great place to work&#x201D;.  &#xD;&#x2028;So I got to shoot a video!!!  &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;This was a very cool way to learn about a company. Not only is it good promotion for what they do, I get to share with you how I saw ImageX during my time there :)  &#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imagexmedia.com"&gt;ImageX Media&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; has created some of the top websites in North America and specialize in Drupal development, which was something that I really enjoyed learning about.  &#xD;&#xD;They were the first &#x201C;boys club&#x201D; that I worked for and have 3 female employees that typically work from home. So it was me, the developers, and my boss for 90% of the week and my gosh, it was a total riot.  What I really enjoyed was the atmosphere these guys created in the office.  Its a tech company, so its a super casual and relaxed even in the way they interact as a team.  They each work on their own project, but collaborate and discuss aloud what they are working on with the rest of the team.  It was neat to hear them talk about things like... the vision they have for the site, how they want viewers to be able to interact and use the site... as well as what they wanted the overall experience to be like.  The whole team worked together and would bring in different knowledge and expertise to each project and it was so refreshing to hear the developers take such pride in the work they produced. Another cool thing is all the employees are heavily involved in the community through volunteering, educating and speaking at different events.  I love that, I think the idea of giving back is so important today, and it is refreshing to see that to the team of ImageX.. its not something they go out of their way to do, giving back is just a part of their every day life, which is something that I also try to do.   &#xD;&#xD;What made me laugh was..... because its Movember right now... most of my coworkers had terrible things happening on their upper lip (but I totally love and support the cause and give props for those raising some mad money for prostate cancer! it just makes all the boys look unfortunate.. for a month... they are all still studs to me the rest of the year!!). But in between working and petting their terrible moustache, these guys would play foosball... &#xD;&#xD;At first.. they would just go to the boardroom to play, close the door and have a blast, then resume work.  But by the 3rd day.. (yea.. it took them 3 days to ask the intern to play...) they asked if I wanted to play foosball with them as well.  Now, I didn&#x2019;t tell them that I just so happened to be homeschool and grow up with a foosball table in the basement... and had a lot of free time.. so when I did play... I kicked ass :) &#xD;&#xD;But what I enjoyed most about the team was the opportunity to be surrounded by people who love what they do.  These guys were so much fun to work with - so considerate and welcoming to share with me what they know, which was a big deal... because by no means am I a developer... sometimes I wish I could be.. I only know like two codes... but these guys took the time to sit me down and tell me what they were working on, and asked for my help on non-technical aspects of their work.  &#xD;&#xD;The end of the week came fast... I think that is because i was laughing, learning and working hard the whole time I was there.  But my boss Glenn treats the office to lunch on Fridays and the team let me pick the type of food I wanted for my goodbye lunch.  We had a little pow-wow in the boardroom and I shared with them the adventures of this project so far as well as a blooper video I made for them... its hilarious :)  &#xD;&#xD;My time with ImageX was really special, I think I felt the closest with these coworkers because I interviewed them and learn about what they do, what they love, and shared a lot of laughs :)  I really felt like i made good friends there, and for that... I am super grateful. &#xD;&#x2028;Glenn messaged me on the weekend and said I had to come to the office to sign some papers today on confidentiality... so after starting my new job.... I had to make my way back to Burnaby to sign these documents.&#xD;&#xD;So I walk in, and Glenn hands me a pen.. I go to sign the sheet and I see this    &lt;---&#xD;&#xD;Not necessarily official... then he says, the real reason he wanted me to come was the ImageX team had a gift for me during my time there... &#xD;&#xD;Gosh, a gift? I should be giving them gifts for putting up with me!!!! I opened the gift box, and the team said they were going to miss me in the office and got me a new iPad for my efforts.  I am so excited, happy, and grateful to have learned from them.  My face hurts from smiling because that was totally unexpected and extremely generous of them.  &#xD;&#xD;I feel so lucky to have been able to meet such a great team of people who were so supportive or me, my project, and my working efforts.  I have had a crazy time in Vancouver, so much more has happened and more to come.  Don&#x2019;t worry, I will be sure to keep you posted. :)&#x2028;&#x2028;Thanks again for reading and following the journey, things are starting to reach the homestretch and I am getting excited to what I am going to be doing next. &#xD;&#xD;Thank you again for your support, I appreciate you!&#x2028;&#x2028;Just Maeghan. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="28_Laughing_too_much_at_work._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="690px" height="523px"/>
</content>
