<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20111109" date="2011-11-09 19:07:19 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Shaking hands, closing deals, making $$&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, November 8, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Hi friends!&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Back in yyc safe and sound after a very eventful but rewarding trip to San Francisco and Silicon Valley.  I can hardly believe a month has gone by since the last time I was here.  I&#x2019;m taking a much needed 5 day break before I start working at the Trico Foundation on Monday, and continue on with the journey.  &#xD;&#xD;I guess that means I have TON to share with you on a really amazing, cool, awesome California Adventure!  Some of you may have seen the video/last blog post on the hotel shooting that occurred two rooms from mine in San Jose.  It was by far one of the most scary and traumatic events that I have ever experienced in my life.  I wish that stress and fear never happen to others, but it sadly does every day.  This is a picture I took when I was trying to leave of all the cop cars out just the front door.. there was more in the back and police stationed on every floor. On top of that stress, I was attacked by a homeless person the following day and experienced my first earthquake in parallel with being ill from stress.  I am sure you are thinking.. what bad luck! And yes, it was terrible luck, but the things that I learned, experienced and people I met during my time in San Francisco made those 5 days of bad luck seem like a steal, and I am so grateful that I can share these next stories and experiences with you. &#xD;&#xD;I was working for Dealmaker Media in San Francisco, a company that creates a network of innovators who see the opportunities in building relationships and sharing knowledge.  They put on several big events like the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://growconf.com/"&gt;GROW Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; in Vancouver, to &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.undertheradarblog.com/"&gt;Under The Radar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; in Silicon Valley with the purpose of connecting startup companies with big players and investors.  It was a great place to work for a lot of reasons.. but some of the highlighting ones can include the work &#xD;space was a loft/apartment --------&gt; &#x2028;check out my tour!&#xD;&#xD;Its awesome being comfortable while &#xD;working... it really does make the world&#xD;of a difference.  That white chair and I &#xD;were best friends for the week and I &#xD;managed to get to get a lot of work &#xD;accomplished.... it was like home &#x2028;schooling! Without the distractions that&#xD;somehow surface when in your own &#x2028;home. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Another aspect I really liked at the&#xD;office was the openness to discussion.  I got to see first hand how improvement through freeform discussion and ideas really enhance the space for innovation and creativity. The Dealmaker team always focused on how good they wanted to be, opposed to how good they were.&#xA0;Which is a motto I live in my life.  :)  It was also so empowering to work for a woman CEO and a team of smart, successful women.  Debbie, Heidi, Lilly, Stephanie, Clare and Giselle were all so welcoming and amazing to work with, I really enjoyed my time there.&#xD;&#xD;Debbie let me sit in on some of the startup companies practice pitches for the Under The Radar event which I REALLY enjoyed.  I got to listen to their presentations and critique them like I used to in &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mtroyal.ca/AboutMountRoyal/MediaRoom/SIFEhelps.htm"&gt;Snatch The Pebble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;, a program I was team leader for with SIFE MRU. After listening to Debbie critique a few, I started to understand what information investors were looking for, and I got to provide my feedback as well as direction to some of these companies that are pitching to VISA, American Express, Google, Microsoft and more.... I&#x2019;m really stoked Debbie believed I could contribute value to her clients like that.&#xD;&#xD;Another thing I feel so grateful for, was being able to work with women who don&#x2019;t act &#x201C;manly&#x201D; or mean to be successful or taken serious in the working world.  I am not a mean person.. and was often told I have to be &#x201C;more mean&#x201D; if I wanted to do well in business.  Debbie and the team are proof that I can stay true to myself and be successful.  There is a huge difference from being honest and standing for what you believe in, to being aggressive and rude when communicating with others.  I was listening to &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=18uDutylDa4"&gt;Sheryl Sandberg on TEDWomen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; about women leaders and why there are so few of them in the workforce (if you haven&#x2019;t seen it.. its wonderful - compliments to my friend Sachin for sharing), but her message about sitting at the table really struck a cord for me.  In short, the point is that women don&#x2019;t negotiate, speak up, or believe they create value in the workplace, which is a contributing factor to why so few women have higher positions. After a week at Dealmaker.. I was surrounded by an office run completely by women, in an industry dominated by men... and these women definitely sit at the table. &#xD;&#xD;This job came at a perfect time, it was the same week that I was featured live on CTV news and published in newspapers across Canada (which I am still blown away by, thank you so much for your interest, kind words and encouragement of this project, I&#x2019;m beyond grateful, thank you so much)... and with that media, a lot of negative comments surfaced about what I am doing as well as, how I managed to get here.  I was really hurt by them, and realized how difficult it can be for women to be recognized for their efforts.  But the team at Dealmaker helped keep my head on straight and also inspired me to keep reaching for the stars. Their support was exactly what I needed during this time of struggle, growth, and learning.  &#xD;&#xD;Exciting news, I&#x2019;ve been asked to help out with the Dealmaker team in Vancouver in two weeks time and I am VERY excited to connect and help out again. &#xD;&#xD;So at the end of the week, I was invited to go to an event that brought some inspiring individuals all together in one room.  It was a &#x201C;TGIF&#x201D; party with Twitter and some really cool people in tech startups around the area.  I&#x2019;m so grateful to have been able to learn and talk with these people and can&#x2019;t even begin to express how much my cheeks hurt after from smiling.   &#xD;&#xD;San Francisco has a contagious atmosphere, people are so willing to help and connect you with others to further your ideas.  Its fast pace there.. when things need to be done.. they get done! I love that.. hahah it is SO true that Canada is much slower pace than the States.. and I see that now.   And finally, the weather... its warm... In Calgary.... it just snowed and I am missing the sun already. :)   &#xD;&#xD;Thanks for reading! I have another blog coming soon talking about my 2nd week visiting Facebook, Google and of course.. eating ice cream. &#xD;&#xD;Stay awesome!&#xD; &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;   &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="8_Shaking_hands,_closing_deals,_making_$$_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
