<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="CFDAB2D0-B371-4474-B995-48F2F6321F85">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120207" date="2012-02-07 17:15:46 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;112 days later... &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, February 7, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;112 + days ago.. I had this idea that some called &#x201C;crazy&#x201D;.  Today, being able to look back and appreciate the fear, the opportunity, the adventure and people who made this idea far more valuable than I had anticipated... thank you. From the bottom of my heart, I appreciate you. &#xD;&#xD;Here is an update on what&#x2019;s going on this week... picking the last company of the project, lining up a job, and what&#x2019;s going on next. :) &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;For those who interested, here is a story and pictures from my trip down to Mexico!&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;The family we were assigned to build the home for was the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZmLeGZNW5KY&amp;feature=youtube_gdata_player"&gt;Bravo-Manzano Family&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;. They come from the poorest part of Mexico and speak a different dialect of spanish.  The father was recently hit by a car (shattered his foot &amp; dented his skull) and put in a position where he was unable to work and provide for the family.  &#x2028;&#x2028;It was so heartbreaking to see these kids... all 8 of them.. sharing 2 beds with their parents, only having one set of clothing.. and shoes that were too small or had holes in them. &#xD;&#xD;In 4 short days, our team built a new home and hope for this family. We provided them with a new clothing, food, and shoes for each member. It was very emotional, and out of the 4 houses I have built in the past, I have never felt this much appreciation and love from the family.  I was really a special trip. &#xD;&#xD;Our team further went into the community to help with a feeding program that serves many children and their families each day. We created food baskets of oil, rice and beans to give to others in the community as well as, donated 8 suitcases full of clothing to those in need.&#xD;&#xD;This was the first time I coordinated a team down there.... and I am so grateful everything worked out.  Each member expressed a new outlook on life and appreciation for giving back. It was truly an amazing experience to disconnect ourselves from our busy lives and focus on the well-being and need of others.  :) &#xD;&#xD;Special thanks to the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.familycharity.ca"&gt;Charitable Foundation of the Family &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;for their support in our fundraising efforts, and all our volunteers and team who made the trip happen. &#xD;&#xD;Stay awesome!!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="7_112_days_later..._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
